<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>one man&#39;s singularity</title>
    <link>https://antweiss.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on one man&#39;s singularity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 15:21:01 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antweiss.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 22 Natan Yellin</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-22-natan-yellin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 15:21:01 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-22-natan-yellin/</guid>
      <description>Natan Yellin - Fixing Kubernetes and the Success of AI Natan Yellin is the CEO of Robusta - a company building an open-source platform for multi-cluster Kubernetes monitoring, troubleshooting, and automation. If you follow him in social media (twitter or linkedin) you&amp;rsquo;ll find that he is very vocipherous about the correct usage of container limits and requests. But from his interview - you&amp;rsquo;ll learn that it&amp;rsquo;s mostly the human experience with Kubernetes (and tech in general) that he cares about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 21 Boaz Ziniman</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-21-boaz-ziniman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 13:39:55 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-21-boaz-ziniman/</guid>
      <description>Boaz Ziniman - Discovering DevOps by Mistake Boaz Ziniman is a Principal Developer Advocate at AWS and one of the first proponents of cloud computing in Israel. Prior to working at AWS he&amp;rsquo;s spent a decade at Zend - the PHP company - also leading the cloudification of Zend services.
Boaz has a great YouTube channel in Hebrew called מעונן חלקית (Partly Cloudy). Check it out here.
Find Boaz on twitter and his own website</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 20 Shauli Rozen</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-20-shauli-rozen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 17:02:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-20-shauli-rozen/</guid>
      <description>Shauli Rozen - Let&amp;rsquo;s Just Get K8S Security Done I first met Shauli when he and his co-founders were only planning to start ARMO - we sat in a small cafe in Ramat Gan Diamond Exchange district and talked about service meshes and network security. Shauli had great ideas and was full of motivation. And it all paid out! Fast-forward 3 years and he&amp;rsquo;s now the CTO of one of the leading Kubernetes security startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Sad Tech Evangelist</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/one-sad-tech-evangelist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 10:50:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/one-sad-tech-evangelist/</guid>
      <description>On Sadness My mom passed away 2 months ago.
The month before that was intense with sadness, fear, hope..
Visiting her in the hospital, watching her suffer one blow after another. She was a strong woman but this was too much even for her. In the end all she wanted was to leave. And leave she did.
The deep sadness of the first weeks is now becoming lighter. It’s still there - just that I don’t feel it all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 019 Steve Pereira</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-019-steve-pereira/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 20:35:17 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-019-steve-pereira/</guid>
      <description>Steve Pereira - DevOps is a MacGuffin Steve Pereira calls himself a Value Stream Guy. Today he is the founder of Visible where he is helping teams define and optimize their value streams. Before that he&amp;rsquo;s been a startup CTO, an agency consultant, a systems and release engineer, a finance IT manager, a tech support phone jockey, and a pizza maker. All focused on the flow of value, all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Directions</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/new-directions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 11:17:41 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/new-directions/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that Time Again I haven&amp;rsquo;t written anything on my personal blog for a while.
Since the start of pandemic it was mostly DevOps Shorts announcements.
But lately I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m changing. Going through another life-period crisis.
On a very positive note - I did some bio-hacking of my own - changed my diet, lost about 6 kilos of body fat and now exercise regularly.
All this gives me renewed energy with which I feel like it&amp;rsquo;s finally time to change my business reailty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 18 Jonathan Hall</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-18-jonathan-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 17:30:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-18-jonathan-hall/</guid>
      <description>Jonathan Hall - Big Ideas for the Little Teams Johnathan Hall (aka TinyDevOps) is a DevOps coach and consultant based in Netherlands. He has almost 3 decades of experience in the IT industry out of which 2 decades were spent in leadership roles. Jonathan is focused on helping small teams do amazing DevOps.
Find him on twitter and on his site
Listen to the episode to learn:
How love of IT is still about making tech do our bidding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 17 Heidi Waterhouse</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-17-heidi-waterhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 10:42:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-17-heidi-waterhouse/</guid>
      <description>Heidi Waterhouse - Future is Just Another Feature Heidi Waterhouse is a prominent figure on the DevOps landscape. And she&amp;rsquo;s also special at that - because her background is neither Dev nor Ops. For the whole of her career she&amp;rsquo;s been a technical writer, a documentation specialist. And I find this wonderfully exciting - because first of all - DevOps has never been the sole concern of Devs and Ops only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 016 Tracy Miranda</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-016-tracy-miranda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 15:25:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-016-tracy-miranda/</guid>
      <description>Tracy Miranda - Fixing Real-World Problems is not as Easy as You Think Continuous Delivery is the practice underlying the DevOps principles. That&amp;rsquo;s why for this episode of DevOps Shorts I&amp;rsquo;m incredibly excited to interview Tracy Miranda - the executive director of the Continuous Delivery Foundation.
Listen to the episode to learn:
How contributing to open-source can help you love your job
How easy it was to set up sane release practices for Jenkins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 015 Viktor Farcic</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-015-viktor-farcic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:22:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-015-viktor-farcic/</guid>
      <description>Viktor Farcic - Defying the Rigid Org Structure Today I&amp;rsquo;m very happy to have Viktor Farcic as my guest. Viktor is the author of the DevOps Toolkit Series, the host of the DevOps Paradox podcast and now also the Developer Advocate at Codefresh
Listen to the episode to learn:
Why software engineers are a rare and lucky breed
How lack of communication skills can make you fall in love with computers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 014 J.Paul Reed</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-014-j.paul-reed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 18:12:22 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-014-j.paul-reed/</guid>
      <description>J.Paul Reed - It&amp;rsquo;s Humans All the Way Down Resilience engineering is one of the most forward-looking topics to surface in our industry in the last 5 years. That&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m so excited to have J.Paul Reed as my guest. Paul is one of the most passionate promoters of resilience engineering practices. He&amp;rsquo;s a co-organizer of REdeploy, a frequent speaker on related topics and now also a senior applied resilience engineer at Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 013 Ohad Maislish</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-013-ohad-maislish/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 15:08:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-013-ohad-maislish/</guid>
      <description>Ohad Maislish - The Revolution of Codified Infrastructure Here&amp;rsquo;s why I was so happy to host Ohad at the show and why his company Env0 is one of my favourite Israeli startups of the last year:
Ohad first reached out to me on Facebook - offering to demo their Infra-As-Code management platform. He was nice, I was curious and we scheduled a half-hour Zoom call. Ohad talked, I liked the platform, provided some (hopefully remotely useful) feedback and we said goodbye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 012 Patrick Debois</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-012-patrick-debois/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 14:01:07 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-012-patrick-debois/</guid>
      <description>Patrick Debois - DevOps as a Life-Changing Methodology Is this the peak of my career as a DevOps show host?!?!
I&amp;rsquo;m excited beyond words - I succeeded to land an interview with the man who invented the DevOps word itself! With the original DevOpsDays orgainzer - the one and only Patrick Debois!
Beside being one of the most prominent DevOps thought leaders of our times, Patrick is now also the DevOps Relations director at Snyk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 011 Philipp Krenn</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-011-philipp-krenn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 14:38:43 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-011-philipp-krenn/</guid>
      <description>Philipp Krenn - Build, Play, Automate This time I&amp;rsquo;m happy to host Philipp Krenn - a meetup organizer, conference speaker and developer advocate at Elastic
Philipp is very good at explaining and demoing exciting new technologies and he&amp;rsquo;s now in the very epicenter of the observability movement - bringing the Elastic stack to engineers all over the virtual world.
Listen to the episode to learn:
What&amp;rsquo;s the role of playfulness in IT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 010 Mark Burgess</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-010-mark-burgess/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 16:54:59 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-010-mark-burgess/</guid>
      <description>Mark Burgess - Digging Away at Human-Machine Systems I&amp;rsquo;m so thrilled! My guest for tonight is Mark Burgess - a &amp;ldquo;technologist, scientist and author, specializing in the physics of Information Systems&amp;rdquo; (quoted from Mark&amp;rsquo;s website).
Mark is probably best known to the IT crowd as the man who defined the ideas behind desired-state configuration management and the creator of the CFEngine CM tool that predated Puppet, Chef and Ansible and is still in use at quite a number of companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Started Wasm IL</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/why-i-started-wasm-il/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 12:29:37 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/why-i-started-wasm-il/</guid>
      <description>I started hearing about WebAssembly a couple of years ago. At first it didn&amp;rsquo;t attract my interest. I thought it was something like a JavaScript framework. But then I got interested in Rust and stumbled upon an article about compiling Rust to WebAssembly.
That&amp;rsquo;s when it occurred to me that WebAssembly had huge potential outside of the browser.
And then WASI got released and Solomon Hykes (the founder of Docker) tweeted this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 009 Adi Shacham Shavit</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-009-adi-shacham-shavit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:37:28 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-009-adi-shacham-shavit/</guid>
      <description>Adi Shacham-Shavit - Quality is Still Too Hard And our guest for tonight is Adi Shacham-Shavit - previously the R&amp;amp;D manager at such companies as AppsFlyer and Lemonade, now EVP Engineering at an early stage startup called Clear.
Adi hates wasting time and making the same mistake twice.
First of all - it makes me happy that Adi is a woman - I feel like my show was lacking in diversity - I only got to interview white men until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 008 John Willis</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-008-john-willis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 17:04:56 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-008-john-willis/</guid>
      <description>John Willis - Towards the 5 Elements of IT This episode of DevOps Shorts is probably the most exciting one I&amp;rsquo;ve recorded until now!
This time I was honoured to host none other but the great John Willis himself - the man who brought DevOpsDays to US, the originator of the CA(L)MS acronym, one of the authors of &amp;ldquo;The DevOps Handbook&amp;rdquo; and now - a senior director at RedHat Global Transformation Office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re on the Cloud Native Landscape!</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/were-on-the-cloud-native-landscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 19:03:49 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/were-on-the-cloud-native-landscape/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re on The Cloud Native Landscape! This is a story about growing together as a community and building a project that matters. Getting into the Mesh About a year and a half ago I got interested in service mesh technology. A customer needed some advanced routing capabilities and we started looking at Envoy and Istio. Then - invitations to talk about Istio at meetups and conferences started flowing in. That&amp;rsquo;s when I got excited about progressive delivery capabilities that service meshes enable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 007 Derek Weeks</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-007-derek-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 19:31:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-007-derek-weeks/</guid>
      <description>Derek Weeks - It&amp;rsquo;s All in The Feedback Loops! DevOps Shorts E007 This time around I was happy to host Derek Weeks - the Vice-president at Sonatype and the co-founder of AllDayDevOps. The man who started doing global virtual conferences before they became cool.
Derek spills some light on what it was like growing up in the Silicon Valley and what DevSecOps really looks like in the real world.
Listen to the episode to learn :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 006 Manuel Pais</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-006-manuel-pais/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 14:51:20 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-006-manuel-pais/</guid>
      <description>Manuel Pais - Exploring the Team Topologies DevOps Shorts E006 About 3 years ago when I started delivering my DevOps Fundamentals training I used to refer to a website called DevOps Topologies in order to explain the different possibilities of applying DevOps to organizational structure. The creators of the site - Manuel Pais and Matthew Skelton did a great job visualizing and explaining the dominant patterns and anti-patterns of building DevOps-ish teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 005 - Mike Druzhinin</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-005-mike-druzhinin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 09:52:33 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-005-mike-druzhinin/</guid>
      <description>Mike Druzhinin - Testing in Production and the Serverless Edge DevOps Shorts E005 Our guest for tonight is Mike Druzhinin - Software Development Manager at Amazon.com and a Program Committee Member of the great DevOops conference.
Mike took a short break from keeping Amazon up and running through the COVID-19 online shopping craze to talk to us about love, DevOps A-HA and the future.
Mike talks about the how playfulness makes IT so loveable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 004 - Carlos Leon</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-004-carlos-leon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 16:41:26 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-004-carlos-leon/</guid>
      <description>Carlos Leon - Hacking the Human Side of DevOps Our guest for tonight is Carlos Leon - an independent cloud native and automation consultant. Carlos is the link between your business and your technical people - because he understands and speaks both languages.
Carlos was born in Colombia, traveled the world and is now based in Netherlands where he is currently helping ING to automate and optimize their software delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 003 - Damien Ryan</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-003-damien-ryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 14:01:24 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-003-damien-ryan/</guid>
      <description>Damien Ryan: Working Sanely to Deliver Small Bits of Value For the third episode of DevOps Shorts I was happy to zoom with Damien Ryan! Damien has spent 22 years working in tech, going from applied science through all kinds of build and release engineering roles to his current position - the Director of Engineering at Featurespace - a company that builds Adaptive Behavioral Analytics technology for fraud and financial crime management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 002 - Baruch Sadogursky</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-002-baruch-sadogursky/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 16:03:07 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-002-baruch-sadogursky/</guid>
      <description>Employ Machines To Do What They Are Good At For the second episode of DevOps Shorts I got to talk to the man with the hat - the great @jbaruch - the Head of Dev Advocacy at JFrog!
Baruch is the person in the very nitty-gritty of DevOps transformation - witnessing firsthand the pains and joys of the largest IT companies out there. This is what makes his perspective so unique and this episode so much worth listening to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devops Shorts 001 - Tobias Kunze</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-001-tobias-kunze/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 09:12:11 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-shorts-001-tobias-kunze/</guid>
      <description>Nurture over Nature A-a-a-nd, we&amp;rsquo;re rolling! The first episode of DevOps Shorts is out!
I&amp;rsquo;m so glad that Tobias Kunze happened to be my first guest! Tobias is the CEO of Glasnostic - a startup with a unique approach to application resilience.
I first encountered Glasnostic (and immediately loved the post-Soviet reference of its name) due to my involvement with service mesh technology. Their company blog has a number of deep finely-written technical posts on meshes and service communication resilience patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extending Envoy With Wasm and Rust</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/extending-envoy-with-wasm-and-rust/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 16:45:18 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/extending-envoy-with-wasm-and-rust/</guid>
      <description>Extending Envoy with WASM and Rust If you already know what Istio, Envoy, WASM and Rust have in common and just want to get started building your filter - feel free to skip straight to part 2 - Building the Filter
Part 1: The Evolution of the Mesh As I’ve mentioned multiple times over the last couple of years - service meshes are the next stage in the evolution of cloud native infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Devops Shorts</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/announcing-devops-shorts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 10:27:51 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/announcing-devops-shorts/</guid>
      <description>DevOps Shorts Welcome to DevOps Shorts: the show where we invite wonderful human beings like yourself to have a lightning-fast talk about Devs, Ops and other mythical creatures.
In the show I will ask you exactly 3 questions and you’ll have 4 minutes to answer each one of them.
If you don’t fit an answer in 4 minutes - you’ll be stopped by a gong, sorry about that :))
If you make it in less than 4 minutes - we’ll use the leftover time for a blitz of totally unexpected questions in the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tangible Devops - Easy?</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/tangible-devops-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 13:29:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/tangible-devops-easy/</guid>
      <description>Tangible DevOps - is it Easy? SpeakEasy or SpeakHard? Last Thursday I had the privilege to be the inaugural guest on the now virtualised DevOps SpeakEasy show . Hosted by none other but the mighty Kat Cosgrove and Baruch Sadogursky - the notorious steampunk fashion icons who also happen to be developer advocates at JFrog.
First of all - it really warms my heart how we suddenly get closer to folks from all over the globe due to COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Week One - The New Reality</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/corona-week-one-the-new-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/corona-week-one-the-new-reality/</guid>
      <description>A New Reality Unfolds Gosh, it&amp;rsquo;s complicated. How do I start this post without sounding banal? We&amp;rsquo;re all confused, aren&amp;rsquo;t we? Even those who say the Corona hysteria is unjustified. Even those who are relatively safe from contagion. Because no matter if anybody I know gets sick or not - there&amp;rsquo;s a new reality our there. Something none of us had to deal with before. How will this impact our communities, jobs, businesses, families, money?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 12:25:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/talks/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s an incomplete list of talks I&amp;rsquo;ve given Many Changes, Little Fun: It’s time to measure the value of DevOps Yalla DevOps 2019, Herzlia, Israel Video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3SEUZ7qUyPE Slides: https://www.slideshare.net/AntonWeiss/many-changes-little-fun WTF Do We Need A Service Mesh Cloud&amp;amp;Edge Native Day Israel, 2019 Video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0zK60iO6WQQ Slides: https://www.slideshare.net/openstackil/wtf-do-we-need-a-service-mesh-by-anton-weiss DevOps Collaboration 2020: Are We in The Trough of Disillusionment? DevOpsCon Munich 2019 Dumb Services in smart Nets: deploy like a Ninja with Istio Service Mesh DevOpsCon Berlin 2019 Slides: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 08:24:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/home/</guid>
      <description>Anton (Ant) Weiss: Blog, Talks, Music and Futurism</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous Career Advice for IT Professionals</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/dangerous-career-advice-for-it-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/dangerous-career-advice-for-it-professionals/</guid>
      <description>Mentor - yes, Career Advice - Not So Sure A large part of my current job involves mentoring, training and coaching less experienced engineers and engineering managers. Most of the time it’s about cloud-native technology, professional mastery, healthy engineering practices and tech blogging/speaking. But sometimes they also come to me for career advice. And I’m definitely the wrong person to come to with that! My career as an employee in tech was far from amazing - rather filled with stress and despair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>devops is a myth</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-is-a-myth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/devops-is-a-myth/</guid>
      <description>DevOps Is A Myth (Practitioner&amp;rsquo;s Reflections on The DevOps Handbook) The Holy Wars of DevOps Yet another argument explodes online around the &amp;rsquo;true nature of DevOps&amp;rsquo;, around &amp;lsquo;what DevOps really means&amp;rsquo; or around &amp;lsquo;what DevOps is not&amp;rsquo;. At each conference I attend we talk about DevOps culture, DevOps mindset and DevOps ways. All confirming one single truth - DevOps is a myth.
Now don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong - in no way is this a negation of its validity or importance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Zero to One with Peter Thiel</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/from-zero-to-one-with-peter-thiel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/from-zero-to-one-with-peter-thiel/</guid>
      <description>Blessed By a Flu I was down with a flu last week. Felt shitty but it was also a blessing of sorts as I got to spend a couple of days in bed reading a book. Gave me an opportunity to complete Peter Thiel&amp;rsquo;s [Zero to One] (http://zerotoonebook.com/). It&amp;rsquo;s widely known that we only remember 10-20% of what we read in books. Even those we really like. I liked Peter&amp;rsquo;s book but not enough to re-read it anytime soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wrap up 2016</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/wrap-up-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/wrap-up-2016/</guid>
      <description>So here I am again - drafting a post on my phone. In fact I&amp;rsquo;ve done this a number of times in the last couple of years. With wordpress it&amp;rsquo;s even perfectly possible to post right away - the mobile app is great. But since I wanted to be geeky and build this blog on Hugo and host on github pages - I&amp;rsquo;ll have to take the extra step. That&amp;rsquo;s exactly what I was talking about at DevOps Days TLV - creativity and geekiness usually don&amp;rsquo;t go hand in hand with efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>measuring devops flow</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/measuring-devops-flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/measuring-devops-flow/</guid>
      <description>During my recent talk at DevOps Days TLV I presented the 12 DevOps Flow Metrics we&amp;rsquo;ve developed for our clients at Otomato.
The feedback was great and I got a number of requests to publish my slides. So we went ahead and created a github pages minisite with all the metrics laid out and explained. We&amp;rsquo;ve aimed at simplicity and conciseness.
Here are the metrics: [http://devopsflowmetrics.org]
Feel free to use and comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 18:11:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome stranger! I&amp;rsquo;m Ant Weiss - an entrepreneur, software delivery consultant, musician, public speaker, writer and instructor.
All this in no particular order and in parallel to being a male human being blessed to have a wonderful family and friends! Yes, we all get on each other&amp;rsquo;s nerves, but that&amp;rsquo;s what makes it fun!
Me I also like to think of myself as a futurist, but aren&amp;rsquo;t we all?
I write on a wide range of topics including but not limited to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>milestone throw</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/milestone-throw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/milestone-throw/</guid>
      <description>Not surprisingly this blog isn&amp;rsquo;t getting too much of my attention. Most of my writing is now around Otomato official blog, evangelism we do for Codefresh, white papers and articles. Oh yes and conference proposals. I&amp;rsquo;ve submitted quite a few lately. There&amp;rsquo;s one talk and a workshop already confirmed for start of December in Munich at DevOpsCon and hopefully there are more to come.
I hope to be able to write more in the next few weeks as we&amp;rsquo;re going on a family trip in the US - which means I won&amp;rsquo;t be doing the day-to-day work for almost a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 months of Otomato</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/2-months-of-otomato/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/2-months-of-otomato/</guid>
      <description>Going forward&amp;hellip;
2 months have passed since I started [Otomato] (http://otomato.link) as a company. Things are going exceptionally well.
We&amp;rsquo;re already working with Motorola, Codefresh, Beame.io, Taboola, Chilli software and more. We are looking to add some bigger logos to this list. We&amp;rsquo;re involved in various types of projects - from large-scale web services to IOT cloud solutions.
Up until now &amp;lsquo;we&amp;rsquo; meant mostly myself alone, but now I also have Eyal David joining me for some of the consulting activities - he&amp;rsquo;s a very strong software delivery shark and it makes me very happy to have him on board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>add sharing buttons</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/add-sharing-buttons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/add-sharing-buttons/</guid>
      <description>this is becoming my official personal blog and I&amp;rsquo;m inclined to post some quality content here. so I better add some sharing buttons. but how does one do this in Hugo?
I recalled I had a [Shareaholic] (https://shareaholic.com/) account I&amp;rsquo;ve used before. Shareaholic is free and very easy to set up.
I&amp;rsquo;ve generated the code snippets from their control interface and pasted them to my theme&amp;rsquo;s layout html files (I&amp;rsquo;m using the wonderfully minimal cocoa theme):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>starting the blog</title>
      <link>https://antweiss.com/blog/starting-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antweiss.com/blog/starting-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been reading the posts on otomato blog - you know that until now it was a mixed bag of professional articles, technical tips and personal impressions.
Now that Otomato is becoming a full-blown consulting firm I feel it&amp;rsquo;s time to separate the personal from the professional.
There still may be some shared context here and there, but starting today I&amp;rsquo;m moving my personal blogging to a Hugo-based site hosted on Github pages (here)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
