<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on one man&#39;s singularity</title>
    <link>http://antweiss.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on one man&#39;s singularity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 23:54:17 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://antweiss.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>2 months of Otomato</title>
      <link>http://antweiss.com/blog/2-months-of-otomato/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 23:54:17 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://antweiss.com/blog/2-months-of-otomato/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Going forward&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 months have passed since I started Otomato as a company.
Things are going exceptionally well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re already working with Motorola, Codefresh, Beame.io, Taboola, Chilli software and more.
We are looking to add some bigger logos to this list.
We&amp;rsquo;re involved in various types of projects - from large-scale web services to IOT cloud solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until now &amp;lsquo;we&amp;rsquo; meant mostly myself alone, but now I also have Eyal David joining me for some of the consulting activities - he&amp;rsquo;s a very strong software delivery shark and it makes me very happy to have him on board. And we&amp;rsquo;ve started training a couple of juniors.
I&amp;rsquo;m also meeting a lot of new exciting people in the field who I hope to partner with one day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And - we&amp;rsquo;re working on a comprehensive DevOps training program with an online academy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And there are more plans which are still early to disclose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this is certainly as stressful as it is great.
A lot to take care of. A lot of responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do get worried from time to time.
There are nights when I wake up and can&amp;rsquo;t go back to sleep because thoughts are running through my head,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it happens less as time passes by.
Growing the company is a challenge - but it&amp;rsquo;s a challenge I&amp;rsquo;m up to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it certainly is too early to make any conclusions. I can just say I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying this new life, no matter how stressful and uncertain it may seem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the journey continues&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>